<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="projectsArray">
        <item>FRIDAYS OF HOPE\n
            "
            "
            Fridays of Hope is an inclusion project where children with special needs in Bucharest
            meet with horses, brass and puppies in the "Star of Hope" horses!

        </item>
        <item>THE CUP WITH CANDY\n
            "
            "
            The Cup With Candy is a yearly campaign on June 1. In 2016, just the first edition, the
            children in hospitals received sweets and cartoons with drawings and encouraging
            messages from nearly 2,000 people!
        </item>
        <item>
            A FAIRYTALE EVENING\n
            "
            "
            A book under your arm, an apple in your hand and a lot of love! Volunteers from all over
            the country and from all corners of the world, along with the Colorful Gang, turn
            ordinary hospital evenings into magical moments!
        </item>
        <item>BOMBOLAND\n
            "
            "
            Bomboland is the most ambitious project of the Candy Taxi. It is where, through
            day-to-day workshops, young people with special needs regain their self-esteem and sense
            of purpose.
        </item>
        <item>THE SOCK WITH CANDY\n
            "
            "
            The last special race of the "Taxi with Candy" in 2017! Between 5th and 7th of December,
            volunteers stopped at all pediatric departments in Bucharest and shared the candy's
            children with candies, kisses and smiles!
        </item>
        <item>PEOPLE FROM THE CANDY TAXI\n
            "
            "
            The Gallery of the West organizes the opening and auction of photos for fundraising for
            the Taxi Association with Candy! Although a recent project, this event is already at its
            second edition!

        </item>
        <item>BABY CUSHION FOR BABY HUMAN\n
            "
            "
            Every year, around Easter, children in pediatric hospitals receive cardboard pillows! It
            is an action through which we want to enjoy the children, but also to awaken their
            curiosity to read!
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>